<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  
  <string name="equipment_body_chainmail_name">Simple Mail</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_chainmail_description">Simple mail. Light, protects from cuts, but it is stitched through with arrows, which makes its owner burst into the melee, where the arrows most likely will not reach him.</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_linotorax_name">Linothorax</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_linotorax_description">A common linothorax, everyone has these. Protects against cuts and, lightly, from arrows.</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_anatomic_armour_name">Anatomical shell</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_anatomic_armour_description">Heavy armor that looks like a muscular body. Perfectly protects owner from arrows, cuts and stabs.</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_lorica_segmentata_name">Lorica segmentata</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_lorica_segmentata_description">The heavy plate armor of the end of the Roman Republic. Perfectly protect the owner, but hold down movement. In addition, it is extremely expensive to manufacture.</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_chestplate_small_name">Small chest plate</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_chestplate_small_description">Just a metal plate attached to the chest. Gives minimal protection, but at least gives it...</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_chestplate_medium_name">Average chest plate</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_chestplate_medium_description">Two small metal plates attached to the chest and back. It gives not such a bad defence, as one might think.</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_chestplate_large_name">Large chest plate</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_chestplate_large_description">Two large metal plates in the shape of muscles, attached to the chest and back. This is almost real armor.</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_none_name">No armor</string>
  <string name="equipment_body_none_description">Just a tunic.</string>
  
  <string name="equipment_helmet_corinthian_close_name">Corinthian Closed Helmet</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_corinthian_close_description">Good protection, but reduce a visibility. Good for phalanx, as the soldiers are covered from the flanks.</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_thrace_open_name">Thracian open helmet</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_thrace_open_description">Average protection, but does not reduce visibility. Such helmets are preferred by swordsmen, as they often have to fight breaking the line.</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_none_name">No helmet</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_none_description">You have no helmets.</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_chalcidian_name">Colchic helmet</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_chalcidian_description">The most common helmet on the territory of the attic. Not the best but not bad</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_imperial_name">Imperial helmet</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_imperial_description">Heavy and well-protective helmet from the time of the Roman Empire.</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_montefortino_name">Montefortino helmet</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_montefortino_description">Early Roman helmet. Better than nothing.</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_phrygian_close_name">Closed Phrygian Helmet</string>
  <string name="equipment_helmet_phrygian_close_description">Probably the best helmet to attack.</string>
  
<string name="equipment_shield_hoplon_name">Hoplon</string>
  <string name="equipment_shield_hoplon_description">Falangite Shield. It gives a very good defence, but it is very hard to attack outside the phalanx.</string>
  <string name="equipment_shield_bakler_name">Iron Buckler</string>
  <string name="equipment_shield_bakler_description">Small shield. Average protection, but does not interfere with swing the sword. Because of the size of the shield, it is better not to fall under fire.</string>
  <string name="equipment_shield_scutum_name">Scutum</string>
  <string name="equipment_shield_scutum_description">Classic Roman shield. It gives a very good defence, but it’s not convenient to move around with it.</string>
  <string name="equipment_shield_thyreos_name">Tureos</string>
  <string name="equipment_shield_thyreos_description">A large oval shield of the Greek type. Gives good protection, not much disturbing the owner.</string>
  <string name="equipment_shield_none_name">No shield</string>
  <string name="equipment_shield_none_description">You have no shields.</string>
  
  <string name="equipment_weapon_doru_name">Douro</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_doru_description">Universal weapon. Effectively and in the phalanx, and if you have to break the line. However, universality has deprived these weapons of high performance in any characteristics.</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_sharp_doru_name">Pointed dora</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_sharp_doru_description">Almost the same as the dora, but much sharper. It’s easier to penetrate armor, but less damage.</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_kopis_name">Kopis</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_kopis_description">Sword with inward bend. It cuts down enemies perfectly, but you will not become like this in a phalanx, as, indeed, with any sword.</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_ksifos_name">Xiphos</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_ksifos_description">Straight short sword. Allows you to deliver both slashing and stabbing strikes, which makes it a balanced attack weapon.</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_sarrisa_name">Sarris</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_sarrisa_description">Pike. A sooo long stick with a sooo sharp tip. Hold have two hands. The ideal weapon for the phalanx, but if you break the line, it becomes a huge problem for its owner. In addition, if the enemy gets close, the pike can not be putted in front of you.</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_wings_sarrisa_name">Winged Harris</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_wings_sarrisa_description">Pike. Due to the winged tip, inflicts terrible injuries, but the armor is harder to penetrate. Hold have two hands. The ideal weapon for the phalanx, but if you break the line, it becomes a huge burden for its owner. In addition, if the enemy gets close, the pike can not be putted in front of you.</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_stick_name">Burnt Stick</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_stick_description">If you burn the end of a stick, it will become stronger. Now you can scare small animals ...</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_forks_name">Forks</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_forks_description">They have no equal, if you want to throw a haystack. In principle, you can stick in the stomach.</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_knife_name">Knife</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_knife_description">useful if you need to cut a piece of bread</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_cudgel_name">Cutgel</string>
  <string name="equipment_weapon_cudgel_description">Thick stick.</string>
  
</resources>