<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="health">Health</string>
  <string name="health_description">Maximum quantity of soldier health in the squad.</string>
  <string name="squadHealth">Squad health</string>
  <string name="squadHealth_description">Squad health</string>
  <string name="armour">Armour</string>
  <string name="armour_description">The value of armour of the defending soldier is  deducted from the  amount of damage of the attacker.</string>
  <string name="baseDamage">Basic damage</string>
  <string name="baseDamage_description">The amount of basic part of the damage, done to the enemy by the soldier.
This damage can de blocked by the armour of the defending soldier.</string>
  <string name="armourDamage">Damage through the armour.</string>
  <string name="armourDamage_description">The amount of the special part of the damage,  done to the enemy by the soldier.  
This damage can't be blocked by the armour.</string>
  <string name="attack">Attack</string>
  <string name="attack_description">The skill of the soldier to attack.  
The skill to conduct successful attack  to the non-defensive target.</string>
  <string name="defence">Defence</string>
  <string name="defence_description">The skill of the soldier to defend himself.
The skill to  override successfully the blow, aimed at the soldier's defeat.</string>
  <string name="defenceHalfSector">Defence sector</string>
  <string name="defenceHalfSector_description">Sector ahead of the soldier, where he can successfully defend himself.</string>
  <string name="missileBlock">Missile block</string>
  <string name="missileBlock_description">Probability to block the projectile successfully.
You should take into account that the shield blocks missiles only during  frontal shelling. Besides, if the shields are not raised,  the chance to block  shelling reduces by half.
The value of frontal shooting is displayed.</string>
  <string name="attackDistance">Distance of attack</string>
  <string name="attackDistance_description">Maximum distance, at which the soldier can do damage to the enemy.</string>
  <string name="speed">The speed of displacement</string>
  <string name="speed_description">Maximum speed of displacement of the soldier in the  squad.</string>
  <string name="acceleration">Acceleration</string>
  <string name="acceleration_description">Acceleration</string>
  <string name="rotationSpeed">Rotation speed</string>
  <string name="rotationSpeed_description">Rotation speed of the soldier  about its axis in degrees.</string>
  <string name="chargeImpact">Charge impact</string>
  <string name="chargeImpact_description">Charge impact. The higher this value is, the higher is the chance to do harm to the enemy and throw back the enemy  during the charge.</string>
  <string name="chargeDeflect">Charge deflect</string>
  <string name="chargeDeflect_description">Charge deflect. The higher this value is, the higher is the chance to do harm to the enemy and throw back the enemy  during the charge.</string>
  <string name="chargeDamage">Charge damage</string>
  <string name="chargeDamage_description">Extra interest of the damage by the soldier's attack, which will be done during successful charge.</string>
  <string name="defenceGoingThrough">Defence by "going through"</string>
  <string name="defenceGoingThrough_description">The skill of defence while going through.</string>
  <string name="flyingSpeed">Flying speed</string>
  <string name="flyingSpeed_description">Flying speed</string>
  <string name="weight">Weight of the squad</string>
  <string name="weight_description">Various landscapes affect the squads of different heaviness in different ways.
Be careful, landscape can both give you the advantage, and become the place of your burial site.</string>
  <string name="weapon_damage">Weapon damage</string>
  <string name="weapon_damage_description">Weapon damage</string>
  <string name="armour_armour">Protection of armour</string>
  <string name="armour_armour_description">Protection of armour</string>
  <string name="missile_block_short">Missile block</string>
  <string name="missile_block_short_description">Missile block</string>
</resources>