<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_dirt_name">Dirt</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_dirt_description">It's difficult to move in the dirt, so,  respectively, it reduces the speed of displacement and defence. 
The heavier the soldiers are, the more difficult it will be for them to move in the dirt.</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_forest_name">Forest</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_forest_description">The heavier the soldier is, the more difficult it will be for him to move, attack and defend and attack in the forest. 
However, light-armed soldiers,on the contrary,  feel at home in the forest.</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_forest_light_name">Open forest</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_forest_light_description">It's more difficult for a heavily-armed soldier to move, defend and attack in the open forest, but these inconveniences are not critical.
Light-armed soldiers  feel themselves a bit more protected in the open forest than in the fields.</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_grass_name">Tall grass</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_grass_description">It doesn't affect the skills  of soldiers, but it's possible to hide easily the whole squad there.</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_road_ground_name">Unpaved road</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_road_ground_description">It's much easier to move along the unpaved road than along the ground, which is not adapted for movements.
It's easier for heavily-armed soldiers to endure  the heaviness of their armor.</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_road_rock_name">Paved road</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_road_rock_description">It's much easier to move along paved road, as it has been made for it. 
Heavily-armed soldiers feel themselves the most safely on such a road.</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_water_light_name">Shallow waters</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_water_light_description">It's rather difficult to make attacks or maneuvers in the water, as it reduces the possibility to attack and displacement speed.
The heavier the soldiers are, the more difficult it will be for them to be in the water.</string>
</resources>