<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
   
  <string name="terrain_modifier_dirt_name">Dirt</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_dirt_description">In mud it is difficult to move, the speed of movement and protection respectively decrease.
The heavier the soldiers, the more difficult they will have in the mud.</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_forest_name">Forest</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_forest_description">The heavier the soldier, the harder it is for him to move, defend and attack in the forest.
However, lightly armed soldiers, on the contrary, feel at home in the forest.</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_forest_light_name">Woodland</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_forest_light_description">It is more difficult for heavily armed soldiers to move, defend and attack in light forest, however these inconveniences are not critical.
Lightly armed soldiers, feel in light forest a little more secure than in an open field.</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_grass_name">Tall grass</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_grass_description">Does not affect the abilities of the soldiers, however, it is easy to hide an entire detachment in it.</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_road_ground_name">Dirt Road</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_road_ground_description">On the road it is much easier to navigate than in unsuitable locations.
To heavily armed soldiers it is easier to bear the burden of their armor.</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_road_rock_name">Causeway</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_road_rock_description">It is much easier to move along the road, because it was created for this purpose.
Heavily armed soldiers feel most protected on such a road.</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_water_light_name">Shallow</string>
  <string name="terrain_modifier_water_light_description">It is quite difficult to make attacks or maneuvers in the water. Falls attack and movement speed.
The heavier the soldiers, the harder they will have in the water.</string>
    
</resources>