<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_death_try_to_follow_the_advices">Try to follow pieces of advice and you'll  do it for sure!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_barricades">Barricades and wood stakes are extremely dangerous!
Barricades can't do much damage, but they are very firm. 
Stakes cause huge damage, but they do it only from  front side.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_basic">You're in charge of the squad, consisting of  thirty soldiers.  
The squad can be reformed into three formations:
free formation, phalanx and testudo.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_how_to_block_arrows">Relocate the squad to the  reference point for the soldiers to confront the shelling frontally and  block as much  arrows as possible.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_close_inventory">Close the inventory</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_congratulations">Congratulations!
Now you know the  basic principles of game mechanics and can succeed in completion of difficult levels!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_drag_equipment">To put the equipment into the inventory or take it out, drag the icon of the  required item to a new place.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_dropped_equipment">After any soldier's death, his equipment  appears on the ground. 
You can pick up the equipment and put it to the invetory, but its amount  can't  surpass the number of soldiers in your squad  in one box.
You can also change current equipment, if the new one is enough for all members of the squad.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_form_info_phalanx">The squad in the phalanx attacks everybody on its way, pushing the enemy back. 
Phalanx is  the most suitable for defence.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_form_info_ranks">The squad is formed into free formation by default. 
The squad is rather maneuvering in free formation, but in case of any damage the soldiers will be  bewildered and won't be able to do anything. 
Free formation is the best for dislocation or attacking  small-numbered enemy  forces.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_form_info_shields">Raised shields are  very efficient for shelling block, but,  in this case, the squad becomes too defenceless in close combat.  Shields block shelling, if the soldiers stand with their  backs  to missiles.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_go_to_camp_exit">Go to the camp exit.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_go_level_exit">Go to the level exit.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_go_to_point">Relocate this squad to the  reference point</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_how_to_open_inventory">Open inventory of the squad, pushing the button in the upper  right corner on the screen.
(If you  press this button  the radius of items search will be displayed in several seconds)</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_minimap_info">You have  the opportunity to view mini maps for land navigation.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_minimap_how_to_use">Open mini map by pressing the corresponding button  at the upper right.
To show the point of displacement  to the squad, touch the required place right on the  mini map.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_open_inventory">Open inventory</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_open_minimap">Open mini map</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_other_formations_dependedn">Other formations depend on the equipment</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_phalanx_side_movement">Phalanx keeps the line in any situation, and sometimes this skill can be rather useful.  
For example, to  overcome formidable obstacles, you can  deploy the squad sideward and  force through without getting damage.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_read_modifyer_panel">Read carefully all modifiers.
In this case you won't have unpredictable outcomes of  the battles!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_how_to_reform_squad">To change the formation press the button in the upper left corner and  swipe towards the appeared button, which corresponds to the desirable  formation.
If it's possible to reform, the squad will be reformed. 
The current formation is displayed on the main button.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_reform_to_phalanx">Reform the squad into phalanx</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_reform_to_shields">Reform the squad into  testudo</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_squad_modifyer_panel">You can get detailed information on each formation and other modifiers, affecting the squad, by clicking the corresponding icon on the panels at the top of the screen.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_squad_phalanx_movement">To move in the phalanx, show direction where to go and what to look at for the squad. During the whole displacement the squad will try to  turn to the indicated direction.
The squad will attack everyone, who will be  on its way.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_squad_ranks_movement">To move in free formation, show direction to the squad. During the whole displacement the whole squad will be  turned towards the direction. 
Enemies will be identified in certain areas around the indicated point. The squad will attack  only identified enemies.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_squad_shields_movement">Handling  of the squad in  testudo formation is equal to handling  in free formation</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_take_a_shields">To have the opportunity to reform into testudo, you need to have shields. 
Pick up shields</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_take_a_spears">To have the opportunity to reform into phalanx, you need to have spears and pikes.
Pick up these spears and substitute your weapons with them.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_watch_equipment_stats">The equipment which is put on affects the characteristics of the squad soldiers and their skill to reform into other formations.
To watch the effect of the equipment, touch the required icon of the item.  To close the window of the characteristics preview  just touch it.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_watch_squad_stats">To find out about the current characteristics  of the squad, press the button with the arrow on the left side of the inventory interface.  
To close the window of characteristics' preview, press the button once again.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_open_squad_modifyer_stats">Open the window of the preview of  the squad characteristics preview.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl1_tutorial_welcome">Welcome to the tutorial of the main mechanics!
Good luck!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_charge_how_to_use">To apply the charge, press the corresponding icon of the skill. 
The soldiers rush to the side, where your squad will be turned to, and in case of confrontation with the enemy, they will do him the damage.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_charge_pikes">These pikemen defend the territory and will try to reform into the phalanx  when approaching.
Apply the charge for fast approach to the enemy for pikemen not to have time to reform.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_how_to_kill_pikes">If you fail to catch the pikemen by surprise, you will suffer serious losses, but if you have the last chance of victory - retreat, provoking the pikemen to reform  into free formation and chase you, then attack again.
Pikemen won't have time to form the phalanx!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_congratulations">My congratulations! 
Now you've mastered the main battle techniques and know how to behave in the most  difficult situations!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_consumables">You are lucky at the moment! You have pilums and charge! 
Pilums are consumables. You can buy them in the store between the levels. You can also improve your squad skills there. The consumables, items and skills  are applied in the same way.  To find out how you can do it, look their description by clicking the icon in the inventory.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_destroy_enemy_on_path">The enemy crossed the road.  Destroy him!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_destroy_marked_enemy">Destroy the indicated enemy squad.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_enemy_pilums">The  enemies  also have consumables and skills.  These ones have pilums!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_go_to_point_1">The shortest way is to the left. Go there.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_go_to_point_2">The road is blocked. You should get around the camp...</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_go_to_point_3">The nearest way to the exit lies through the narrow passage.  Go there.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_go_to_point_after_fight">It would be a good idea to reinforce your squad after the stiff battles. 
Go to the indicated point.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_go_to_point_exit">Go to the exit</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_how_to_open_squad_main_info_panels">To show or remove the panels of enemy squads' characteristics, press the corresponding button on the right of the screen.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_look_to_enemy_end_regroup_to_phalanx">Face the enemy and then reform into the phalanx.
Destroy the enemy</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_open_squad_main_info_panels">Switch on visualization of the panel of enemy squads' characteristics.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_phalanx_defence">Phalanx is a defensive formation. 
When retreating in phalanx facing the enemy, you will be able to hold even against superior forces.
However, if you are armed with pikes, the phalanx feels great during the attack.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_pikes">The passage is shut by the pikemen. If the pikemen formed the phalanx,  no one has chances to confront in  a straight fight against each other.  
There are only two variants: whether to attack them, while pikes are not lowered yet  (then they won't be able to reform into  the phalanx), or  shoot them down from a distance (as the pikers can't use their shields)</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_pilums_how_to_use">To throw pilums to the enemy, press the button with their image and, with the  finger fixed on the screen, drag it to the side of the enemy. Then take the finger  off the screen.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_retreat_and_regroup">Retreat to the indicated position and regroup</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_shoot_pikes">These pikemen have already formed into the phalanx.  The best way to win them  is to shoot them down at the distance.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_squadless_unit">Except the enemies you have neutral soldiers.  They can reinforce your ranks. 
To reinforce your squad, reform it into free formation and single out neutral soldiers. When they come up, they will join you. 
The squad must be out of battle</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_squad_main_info_panel_icons">Each mentioned characteristics has its own icon. The higher characteristics is, the larger number of icons will be visible.
1 icon - small value, 2 - mean value, 3 - large value</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_squad_main_info_panels">To find out more about your enemy, you have the panel, which shows the main characteristics  of the enemy squad: his weapons, formation, skills and consumables</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_squad_phalanx_movement">To move in the phalanx, show the squad where to go and to look at. During  the whole displacement the squad  will try to turn to the indicated direction. 
The squad will try to attack everybody on its way.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_squad_ranks_movement">To move in free formation show direction to the squad. During the whole displacement the squad will try to turn to the indicated direction. 
Enemies will be identified in certain areas around the indicated point. The squad will attack  only identified enemies.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_squad_shields_movement">Handling  of the squad in  testudo formation is equal to handling   in free formation</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_squad_surround">Prevent from being trapped!  Soldiers can't defend their backs. If you are trapped, more likely, you'll lose.
In such situation it's better to retreat and regroup to confront the enemy.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_take_shields_and_attack">Sometimes  definitely losing situation occurs.  
In such case it's better to avoid fighting and  quit the level. Be careful, charge can be applied only  in free formation!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_take_units">Reinforce the squad with new soldiers</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl2_welcome">Thus, here you'll learn  the main offensive postures, usage of consumables and skills of the squad. 
Good luck</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_congratulations">Congratulations!
Now you've mastered all basic principles of the game and succeed in  passing difficult levels!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_destroy_enemy">Destroy the enemy</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_forest_be_carefull">A very heavy squad gets heavy fines in attack and defence in the forest, for this reason  you have  the advantage over the enemy.
However, the enemy still has strong armour and destruction power, so be careful.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_go_to_enemy_1">The way to the exit is blocked by the enemy squad. You must destroy it.
Go to the enemy squad</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_go_to_exit">Go to the exit</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_go_to_forest">This enemy squad is very heavy. He has the advantage even on the neutral territory, not to mention the road. 
To even the odds, draw the enemy into the forest. Pay attention to the panel of enemy squad characteristics, look  how characteristics change under the influence of the terrain.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_go_to_forest_enemy">Draw the enemy into the forest</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_go_to_road">Go to the forest</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_take_heavy_equipment">Come back to the destroyed enemy and put on his equipment to make your squad heavy</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_take_units">There is a neutral camp at the top. Reinforce your camp there.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_terrain_base">Except the neutral terrain  there's  the terrain, which affects the squad characteristics. 
All the current characteristics are displayed on the squad's panel of modificators.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_terrain_forest">Each terrain affects the squads of different heaviness in different way.  For example, forest gives all the advantages of the attack and defence to light squads and fines to heavy squads.
Fine for the displacement speed is imposed on all the squads.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_terrain_other">Except the terrain, which gives advantages, there is the terrain, which imposes fines only.   For example, water and dirt. Try to avoid  such terrain and draw the enemy there.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_terrain_road">The road allows to move quicker. Besides, it gives advantages to heavy squads in the attack  and defence</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_terrain_road_heavy">Having heavy armor and benefits due to the road, you will easily do away with light squads of the enemy, which outnumber you.
To meet light squads, come into position on the road.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_weight_base">Any item of the equipment item has its weight. Total weight of the equipment affects heaviness of the squad. 
Heaviness of your squad is displayed on the modificators panel of the squad.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_lvl3_welcome">Hence, here you'll find out about heaviness of the squads, terrain influence on them, as well as  learn how to use the advantages  and fines of the terrain. 
Good luck!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_zones_pages">Pages of the store</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_zones_score">Your gold, silver and squad experience</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_zones_settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_main_page_name">Tradesman</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_main_page_desc">Here you can buy and sell equipment and consumables.
 You can see characteristics of the squad wearing equipment. 
You can see all opened and unopened items of equipment.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_hospital_name">Hospital</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_hospital_desc">Here you can heal wounded soldiers.  (In future,  you'll be able to reinforce the squad with contractors for gold )</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_studies_name">Gymnasium</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_studies_desc">Here you can train your soldiers for new skills.  Skills of the squad is one of the components of success!
You shouldn't underestimate their force.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_stats_train_name">Boot camp</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_stats_train_desc">Here you can train soldiers, improving their main characteristics.  The higher soldiers' characteristics are, the higher chances are to win the battle!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_zones_donate_name">Market</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_zones_donate_desc">Here you can exchange gold for silver or  scrolls with priceless value. You also can earn gold in different ways :)</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_play_page_name">Camp</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_play_page_desc">Your adventures  will start from this place. Good luck!  (You can also access the main menu from here..)</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_do_go_to_studies">Go to the page Gymnasium</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_do_buy_pilums">Buy pilums</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_do_buy_shield">Buy shields</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_do_open_shield_page">Open tap page of shields</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_drag_drop">To buy or sell the item drag it with you finger here.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_drag_drop_equipmant">You can drag the equipment to the  equipment zone</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_drag_drop_consumables">Consumables can be dragged to the consumables zone</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_equipmant_pages">Filters of equipment</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_all_equipmant_page">All opened and unopened equipment</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_equipmant_market">Equipment for sale</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_consumables_market">Consumables for sale</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_player_stats">Characteristics of your squad with current equipment and formation</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_playes_consumables">Your consumables</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_player_equipmant">Your equipment</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_market_player_inv_equipmant">Equipment in your inventory</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_hospital_squad_state">Condition of soldiers in your squad. Green -healthy, red - badly wounded.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_hospital_heal_squad">Pay silver to the  doctors and they heal your soldiers</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_hospital_order_to_heeal">Show the doctors who to treat first.
If you don't have enough money to heal all of them, it can affect their future battles</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_player_skills">Used skills of your squad</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_all_skills">All available skills</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_skill_page">Press the icon of the skill to highlight it and open its page</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_skill_desc">Press the icon of the highlighted skill to watch the description and characteristics of the skill</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_skill_opened_page">The page of chosen skill</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_skill_upgrade_tree">Here you can watch the tree of skill improvement, unlock and improve the skill of the squad</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_skill_unlock">To unlock the skill, study the first node in the village of improvement</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_skill_drag_drop_take">To choose the unlocked skill for its use, drag it from the slot of all skills to the slot of the squad</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_skill_drag_drop_drop">To choose the unlocked skill, drag it from the slot of the squad skills</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_kill_do_unlock">Unlock the skill</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_skill_do_take">Choose the open skill for the use</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_skill_do_open_another_page">Open the page of another skill</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_studies_skill_do_go_to_play">Open the page of the camp</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_training_page_desc">To improve characteristics of the squad, press the corresponding buttons</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_training_stat_name">Characteristics</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_training_stat_value">Current value</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_training_stat_add_value">The level of change after improvement</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_training_stat_cost">The cost of improvement</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_training_stat_whole_progress_bar">Green bar means the number of improvement levels, you've mastered out of all possible ones.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_tip_training_stat_level_progress_bar">Yellow bar means the amount you've paid for the opening of a new level of improvement</string>
</resources>